oppsource.com 2019-07-13

# OppSource Sales Engagement | Privacy Policy

In this Privacy Policy we, OppSource.com, Inc. (“OppSource”), describe our data collection and usage practices with respect to information we collect from visitors of web and mobile sites on which we post this Privacy Policy, including at http://oppsource.com (the “Site”), or using other products or services we provide (“Services”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to data that we collect through other means, including data that we collect offline or via web or mobile sites on which we do not post this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, then you must not access or use the Services. Our Services may be offered through or in connection with third-party mobile applications or third-party websites. When you participate in the Services you are leaving the third-party mobile application or website through which you accessed the Services.

**Information Collection**

_When you consent to our collection of your personal data on this Site, OppSource.com, Inc. is what’s known as the ‘controller’ of the personal data you provide to us._

_Usage and Browsing Information Your Devices Transmits_. You can visit our Site without registering or actively submitting personal data to us. If you do not register, general technical user data, such as your device’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type, and the date and time of your visit, may be automatically collected through the use of “cookies” (small files that are stored on your computer by a website to give you a unique identification) or other technologies. Cookies also keep track of Services you have used, record registration information regarding your login name and password, record your preferences and keep you logged into the Site.

_Information You Actively Submit_. If you register on our Site on behalf of a corporate customer or partner or if you sign up for our newsletter, blog or webinar, you will provide contact information such as your name, email address, phone number, mailing address and company affiliation.

_Combination_. We may combine information that your device transmits, information that you actively submit, and information that we obtain from third-party sources when you provided those sources permission to pass that information to us.

**User Feedback**

If you provide us with comments, suggestions, recommendations or other feedback pertaining to our Services (collectively “Feedback’), you understand that we may (although we have no obligation to do so) retain, disclose, use, or otherwise commercially exploit that Feedback in connection with any or all of our Services without any compensation or consideration to you.

**Information Tracking Technologies**

We may use, and allow third parties to use, web beacons on our Site to improve the performance of the Site and our Services. Web beacons are small, graphic images on web pages, web-based documents, or in email messages that allow us or third parties to monitor who is visiting our Site or if an email has been read. Web beacons collect the IP address of the device that the web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the web beacon comes from and the time it was viewed. Web beacons may be linked to your personal information. We may also use third-party devices, links or electronic mail, to improve the quality of content on our Site and our Services. These third-party devices may use cookies, web beacons or other technology to collect information about your visits to our Site (or other sites). We may collect traffic information and data on and from the use of third parties sites. OppSource may use a pixel or cookie to examine what is happening on third-party websites, including programs and sites with marketing and advertising partners, to improve the understanding of site traffic at a granular level and market research effectiveness. Customers or partners that are hosted on, accessed by or routed through the Site should consult the privacy and other policies of third parties through whom they are providing information. You can opt-out of receiving interest-based ads and tracking from third parties who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self- Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website. (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, and our Site are not currently set up to respond to those signals for tracking on our website.

**Information Usage**

We use your information to operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and Services; enhancing and improving our Services; managing our communications; and analyzing our products and Services).

If you provide us with your name and contact information, we will use this information to answer requests from you, communicate with you regarding any Services we are providing to you as well as inform you about new products and Services (unless and until you opt-out of marketing information).

We may also use information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies to determine your interests in particular advertisements and other communications.

Sometimes we will use your information after collecting your consent on our Site. Other times, OppSource will process your data when it is in our legitimate interests to do this and when these interests do not override your rights.

**Information Sharing**

Information associated with your name we share only as follows:

  * With your opt-in consent.
  * We use affiliated and unaffiliated service providers all over the world that help us deliver our Services and run our business subject to confidentiality agreements.
  * We will disclose data as required by law or to protect you, other users, us or third parties from harm, including fraud, data security breaches or where someone’s physical safety seems at risk.
  * In a reorganization or sale of our company or assets, your data may be transferred, subject to the acquirer accepting the commitments made in this Privacy Policy and in compliance with applicable law.

Also, we freely share aggregated and anonymized usage statistics that cannot be used to identify you individually.

**Children and Minors**

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from persons under the age of 13. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on our Site.

For EU/UK data subjects: The Site is not intended for children under the age of 16, and we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from persons under the age of 16 from the EU or UK.

If you are a parent or legal guardian who discovers that your child has provided us with any of the foregoing, you may reach us at contactus@oppsource.com, and we will promptly delete such information from our files. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13 or 16 (in the EU/UK), please reach us at contactus@oppsource.com.

**Information Security**

We attempt to safeguard and protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction, through maintenance and use of reasonable security measures. However, please bear in mind and be aware that unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and the inherent insecure nature of the Internet, among other factors, may potentially compromise the security of your information at any given time. As such, we cannot make any guarantees as to the security of your information.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to external websites, and areas where you can provide information to third-parties. These are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or third-party sites. Any personal information you provide in such areas, and on such linked pages is provided directly to that third-party and is subject to that third-party’s privacy policy. Please learn about the privacy and security practices and policies of external websites and third-parties before providing them with personal information.

**Opting out**

If you want to withdraw a consent previously provided to us, or otherwise do not wish to (1) receive marketing communications from us, or (2) participate in any of OppSource’s Services, please [click here](mailto:marketing@oppsource.com) to receive an opt-out cookie. OppSource’s platforms and systems are cookie based, so for the opt-out to work for you, your browser must allow third-party cookies.

**Updating, Correcting, or Deleting Your User Profile and Password**

If you register as a Client or Partner, you can update, correct, or delete your user information and email subscription preferences by going to the contactus@oppsource.com section of our Site.

**Effective Date and Changes**

This Privacy Policy is effective May 25, 2018 and we will modify it from time to time. We will notify you of such changes by posting the updated Privacy Policy on our Site. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date found at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check this Privacy Policy periodically, to inform yourself of any changes to it. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy become effective will indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**Additional Information**

If you have questions about this Policy, or the practices of or your dealings with the Site, please email contactus@oppsource.com. For more general information, you can reach us at contactus@oppsource.com or write us at the following address:

OppSource.com, Inc.

370 Wabasha Street North, Suite 640

Saint Paul, MN  55102

OppSource will address all questions, complaints or requests concerning this Privacy Policy within 30 days of receipt.

For EU/UK citizens, please use contactus@oppsource.com to inquire about your rights.

Last Modified: May 25, 2018.

Copyright 2018, OppSource.com, Inc.

All Rights Reserved.
